Ohhh ah
Ohhhh aaahhh
You know you love me,
I know you care
Just shout whenever
And ill be there
You are my love,
you are my heart
And we will never
ever ever be apart
Are we an item
Girl quit playin
We're just friends
What are you sayin
Said theres another
and looked right in my eyes
My first love broke my heart
for the first time
And I was like
baby baby baby ooooh
Like baby baby baby nooo
Like baby baby baby ooooh
I thought you'd always be
mine, mine
Babybaby baby oooh
Like baby baby baby nooo
Like baby baby baby ooooh
I thought you'd always be
mine, mine
Oh for you I would
have done whatever
And I just cant believe
we aint together
And I want to play it cool,
but im loosing you
Ill buy you anything,
ill buy you any ring
And I mean please say,
baby fix me
And just shake me till you wake
me from this bad dream
Im goin down down down down
And I just cant believe my first
love wont be around
And im like baby baby baby ooooh
Like baby baby baby nooo
Like baby baby baby ooooh
I thought you'd always be
mine, mine
Baby baby baby oooh
Like baby baby baby nooo
Like baby baby baby ooooh
I thought you'd always be
mine, mine
LUDA.
When I was 13,
I had my first love
There was nobody that
compared to my baby and
nobody came between us or
could ever come above
She had me goin crazy, oh I was
star struck She woke me up
daily, don't need no starbucks
She made my heart pound,
and skip a beat when I see
her in the street
and, At school
on the playground,
but I really wanna see her on
the weekend She know she
got me dazing, cause she
was so amazin And now my
heart is breakin,
but I keep on sayin
Baby baby baby oooh
Like baby baby baby nooo
Like baby baby baby ooooh
Thought you'd always be
mine, mine
Baby baby baby oooh
Like baby baby baby nooo
Like baby baby baby ooooh
Thought you'd always be
mine, mine
Im gone
(yea yea yea) (yea yea yea)
(Repeat 3x) Now Im all gone
Gone. gone
Im gone.